icoholder.com 2019-04-19

# Privacy policy - ICOholder

Your privacy is critically important to us. At ICOholder, we have a few fundamental principles:

\- We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.

\- We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the ongoing operation of one of our services.

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact us.

## **Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, ICOholder collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available. While providing our services we collect:

\- Your Browser type

\- Your Language preference

\- Referring site 

\- Date and time of each request

\- Your IP address 

ICOholder’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how ICOholder’s visitors use its website. 

ICOholder also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comment. ICOholder only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that expert IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the website.

## **Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to ICOholder’s websites choose to interact with ICOholder in ways that require ICOholder to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that ICOholder gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up as experts and/ sign up in as ICO team member or sign up for newsletters and/or submit ICOs to provide an email address. In each case, ICOholder collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with ICOholder. ICOholder does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. While providing our services we collect:

\- Your username 

\- Your e-mail address 

\- Your Facebook / Linkedin profile link

\- Your profile picture

## **Aggregated Statistics**

ICOholder may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. ICOholder may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, ICOholder does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. We store and process your data on the territory of the US.

## **Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

ICOholder discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on ICOholder’s behalf or to provide services available at ICOholder’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using ICOholder’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Some of these services include commercially available remarketing services (for e.g. Facebook Custom Audience). ICOholder will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, ICOholder discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request. If you have submitted your email address for newsletters or you have registered as an expert on the website, ICOholder may occasionally send you an email to tell you about news, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with ICOholder. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. ICOholder takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## **Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. ICOholder uses cookies to help ICOholder identify and track visitors, their usage of ICOholder website, and their website access preferences. ICOholder visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using ICOholder’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of ICOholder’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## **Business Transfers**

If ICOholder’s, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired right to use user`s information is transferred to acquirer. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of ICOholder may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## **Ads**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by ICOholder and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## **Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, ICOholder may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in ICOholder’s sole discretion. ICOholder encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.

Last change: 2017-12-05
